What's the matter?
Uh... Something in my ear.
Can you hear me, Yuji Itadori?
Listen and—
Wait, wait, wait! I'm your ally, you idiot!
It's me, Mechamaru from the Kyoto school!
There's no time.
Listen and understand the first time.
Satoru Gojo has been sealed.
Goodnight, Satoru Gojo.
We'll meet again in the new world.
Maybe for me.
But it's time for you to wake up already.
How long will you keep letting it
have its way with you, Suguru?
Incredible!
This is a first!
Hey, Geto.
Mahito, look at this.
You proposed that the soul
exists before the body,
but actually, the body is part of the soul,
and the soul is part of the body.
There's no other way to
explain this phenomenon
or the fact that the body's memories flow
into my brain after I swap hosts.
Does that really have to be a universal truth?
Are you sure the world doesn't operate
differently for your technique and mine?
So each technique is its own world-view?
I like it. What a lovely idea.
Hey!
If you're going to do this, hurry it up.
Not only is it absolutely foul,
but the view here is awful, too.
I wanted to enjoy this
sight for a bit longer, but...
Indeed, I wouldn't want anything to happen.
Gate, Close.
Now we can't use this anymore, right?
Yeah, it only holds one.
Unless the man inside kills
himself, it's unusable now.
Huh. Lame.
Well, in any case...
The sealing is complete.
Episode 34
Pandemonium
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
We're talking about Satoru Gojo here.
What proof do you have
for me to believe you?
Sorry, but I have nothing.
If I must provide something,
it's the very fact that I'm here.
I was killed on October 19th
by the special-grade
cursed spirit called Mahito.
What's here is now is no more than the
insurance I left when I was still alive.
Advanced insurance, yes.
So I had no choice but to
set its condition for activating to
"after Satoru Gojo has been sealed."
To decrease the risk of it not going off,
I only managed to sneak these puppets
into three locations ahead of time.
Yuji Itadori was the Jujutsu High sorcerer
least likely to be leaking any information.
And Mei Mei, given the situation,
I'm now certain you're in the clear, too.
Why?
Because someone as skilled
at intelligence gathering as you
was dispatched here to Meiji Shrine Station
instead of acting in the shadows at Shibuya.
Itadori wasn't even a part of Jujutsu
society until several months ago, either.
Hey, that might have been so I'd have
an excuse to refuse aiding them.
Besides, I'm the one who has
kept stopping Itadori-kun
from heading straight
to Shibuya all this time.
Even if we were ordered to be on standby.
Then why...
is a curse user currently heading
your way to eliminate you?
One, two... Two, huh?
Itadori-kun, which is stronger, these two
or the cursed spirit you fought earlier?
They're probably stronger
than that grasshopper.
Apparently, the cursed spirit Itadori-kun
fought was able to speak human language,
so it was semi-first-grade or higher, at least...
and things like that are
crawling out of the woodwork?
I wonder where they've been hiding
and what they've been up to until now.
Let's ignore the curse users
and move onward.
We need to confirm Gojo-kun's status first.
Don't.
The situation in Shibuya has already changed.
Their barrier techniques are
several degrees better than ours.
Shibuya Station
There are currently four
veils lowered over Shibuya,
A: the veil trapping common people inside,
B: the veil trapping Satoru Gojo inside,
C: the veil keeping sorcerers from entering,
and D: another veil like A to keep
common people trapped inside.
And you're saying the area further
down these tracks is blocked by C.
That's right.
The sorcerers on standby are
already inside the veil, right?
And you can't use cell phones inside the veil.
Looks like that's not all, either.
I can't get a hold of the assistant supervisors
who are supposed to be outside the veils.
Please, just follow my directions.
This insurance of mine won't last long.
Please.
Mei-san.
All right, tell us.
Itadori, return to Meiji Shrine Station,
and head to Shibuya from the surface.
Tell all the sorcerers there
about Gojo being sealed.
Get them to share our
goal of recovering Gojo.
Right!
Mei Mei, create an opportunity
for Itadori to escape.
After defeating the curse users,
I'd like you to follow
this track, for starters.
But I don't know what moves
the enemy will make.
So adapt and respond.
By the way, they haven't frozen
your bank account yet, have they?
Huh?
If Satoru Gojo disappears, both jujutsu
and human society will be upended.
I'm sorry, but please stake your life on this.
And I even thought that
would be worth it once...
I was the worst.
Hey, what about me?
Follow whichever one you prefer.
Okay, Nee-sama it is!
Everyone, they're here.
You're Mei Mei, right?
Go ahead and do as you please.
I'll match you.
Thanks!
21:26 Tokyo Metro, Shibuya Station B5F, Shin-toshin Line Platform
Looks like you're all awake.
Now, for our next...
What's wrong?
I can't believe this guy!
Looks like physical time
isn't passing inside here.
Man, I screwed up.
This is all kinds of bad.
Well, it'll all work out somehow.
I'm counting on you, everyone.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
21:22 Shibuya
True...
Even accounting for those
trapped inside the station,
the crowd density was low.
So the transfigured humans were
lying in wait inside the buildings,
and now they've started attacking
the non-sorcerers, huh?
That's why we've stopped
standing by and started to act.
There wasn't much else we could do.
Our response is falling too far behind.
But my biggest concern is...
The veil—
The veil keeping sorcerers out
that lowered at the same time, right?
It's been some time since
Gojo-sensei arrived at the site.
Why did they choose now, of all times?
Either something has happened inside
or they needed to wait for this
moment as part of their strategy.
All I can say for certain is
that these aren't the types
to face us without a plan.
I'll focus on the enemies
who lowered the veils.
You two, please rescue all
the common people you can.
All Three Teams Enter Simultaneously
Yes. Right.
Once you've confirmed the situation,
please exit the veil again, Nitta-san.
With signal blocked inside,
we'll constantly need
someone on the outside.
I would like you to take on that role.
We'll do whatever it takes
to establish a communication network
using just the assistant supervisors.
It should be possible if we
mobilize those off-duty
and a portion of our windo—
Yah!
Man, bullying the weak really
is the best job for me!
This is what you all want, right?
Yes.
Please continue hunting down all
the humans in suits outside the veil.
Okay!
And I can go inside once I'm finished, right?
What's this? What's going on?
The sealing is complete.
However, the Prison Realm still
hasn't finished processing
all of the information that is Satoru Gojo.
We won't be able to move it for a while.
They got one over on us.
Itadori, good news!
Huh?
They can't move Gojo from
where he was sealed on floor B5.
21:27 Between Meiji Shrine and Shibuya Stations
Why not?!
Because he's Satoru Gojo.
Makes sense!
Let's encircle them.
We'll have sorcerers follow the subway lines
into Shibuya Station from
each neighboring station.
Shin-toshin Line
Meiji Jingu Station
Fukubumon Line
Omotesando Station
Seiyoko Line
Daikanyama Station
Den-en-toshin Line
Ikejiri-ohashi Station
Shibuya Station
Then, once the veil keeping sorcerers
out is lifted, we charge in.
Have them follow them?
But I can't get a hold of Ijichi-san!
Oh...
What?!
Hey, who was sent to Shibuya?
Well...
Kill me.
D-D-D-Did you call for me?
Nanamin!
Nanamin, are you here?!
Itadori?
N-Nanamin?
Gojo-sensei...
has been sealed!
...has been sealed!
Sealed?!
You two, change of plans.
We meet up with Itadori-kun at once.
If it's true that he's been sealed,
then it's over.
For every human in this country.
Man, now they know what we're doing.
The sorcerers are going to
come here in force now.
I'll be staying behind.
What about the rest of you?
I'm getting revenge for my younger brothers,
and killing Yuji Itadori and Nobara Kugisaki.
Then I'll go get the rest of my brothers from
where they're being kept in Jujutsu High.
I don't care about this Kugisaki,
but you can't kill Itadori.
We're turning him into Sukuna.
Not my problem.
Jogo, calm down.
Honestly, I think I want to kill Itadori, too.
Mahito! What are you—
From what I could tell after
seeing Satoru Gojo in person,
now that he's sealed away, the sorcerers
and cursed spirits are evenly matched.
If Sukuna is resurrected,
we'll have a huge advantage,
and victory is basically ours, right?
Well, that's true.
But then,
that also means we're perfectly capable of
winning with the forces we have now, right?
So let's kill Itadori!
It'll be fine!
Even if we lose Sukuna, we can still win.
Are you serious?
As serious as can be.
I don't need to be the one smiling
in the wasteland a century from now.
As long as curses can live as people,
that's all that matters.
Sukuna isn't our ally.
We might even be the ones facing
greater risk if he is resurrected.
But if Sukuna is resurrected, that's
guaranteed to usher in the age of curses.
We are not like the humans of today.
We do not fear death,
and we follow the path to
our goals without falsehoods.
That is the essence of us curses
that those fakes lack.
You're wrong.
Wha?!
No matter how off-kilter or inconsistent,
we always act in accordance
with our true desires.
That's what it means to be a curse.
Oh, when I said you were wrong,
I meant regarding what curses are.
I agree, the whole resurrection
thing is one possibility.
Nor do I really want to fight you over it.
So how about we play a game?
If I run into Itadori first, I'll kill him.
If you find him first, you can give him the
fingers and let Sukuna regain his power.
And if I find him first, I kill him. That okay?
Hey!
Oh! You want in, too, Choso?
That's fine, of course.
You're more on Jogo's side
if you had to pick, right, Geto?
What about you?
I have to stay here and watch
over the Prison Realm.
So I'll abstain.
Do whatever you'd like.
As far as I'm concerned,
Sukuna was just the alternative
if the Prison Realm failed.
This is ridiculous.
All the sorcerers, even Itadori,
will be heading this way to save Gojo.
So all you have to do is wait here.
This won't even be a game.
Ready, go!
Wha—Wait up!
Those cursed spirits are
smarter than you two.
Give him back.
We cooperated with you and
kept dropping monkeys for you.
Now give us back Geto-sama's
body like you promised.
Don't toy with...
...Geto-sama any further.
Obviously, I'm not giving him back.
I don't recall leaving your heads empty, too.
Next time you make a promise with a sorcerer,
you should make it clear that it's a pact.
Now, begone.
Or do you want to be killed by this body?
You'll regret this.
Regret, huh?
Now...
How did that taste again?
Nanamin!
Na-na-min! Na-na-min!
Na-na-na-na-na-na-min!
Hey.
Hey!
Na-na—
Fushiguro! Nanamin!
And... who?
You really were referring to
Nanami-san with that "Nanamin," huh?
Geto-san did?
To be more precise, the thing
that's living within Suguru Geto.
The inside of Shibuya Station
is currently a real Pandemonium.
It's full of those special-grades,
the cursed spirits they brought with them,
the curse users tied to Geto,
as well as transfigured humans
and normal people.
In that case, it would be
faster to attack through
the subway from the neighboring stations.
But in order to do that,
we need to lift that veil first.
It's an emergency.
Please multi-task.
I guess this isn't the time for complaining.
There are several requests only
a first-grade can fulfill.
I'll step outside and take care
of all those with Ijichi-kun.
During that time, I want
you three to do something
about the veil keeping sorcerers out.
Ino-kun.
Kusakabe-san and Zen'in's special first-grade
sorcerer should be inside this veil, as well.
If you're able to meet up with them,
please tell them about the situation
and request their help.
I think they already understand the situation,
though, thanks to that shouting.
Roger that!
Also, please take care of these two.
I will!
Ino-san?
Nanami-san is counting on me!
You two!
Before we start the mission,
let me make it clear how important this is.
The two main issues with losing Gojo-san...
First, the collapse of the Gojo clan.
The Gojo clan is currently a one-man
team of Satoru Gojo himself.
There are also lots of
sorcerers who have been saved
due to Gojo-san's influence, pride, and whims.
Throughout Heaven and Earth, I Alone Am the Honored One
Itadori, you're one of those sorcerers, right?
Yeah!
So casual about it!
All of those people are going to
find themselves in trouble,
and, worst case, eliminated!
That brings us to issue two:
the collapse of the power balance.
All of the cursed spirits
and curse users who've
been keeping quiet because
Satoru Gojo was around
will start taking action all at once.
Now, if those guys from
issue two try starting a war
while society's in disarray
from fighting over issue one,
we'll lose.
That's the future as Nanami-san and I see it.
So what do you think happens if we lose?
At the very least, the age of humans
would probably be over for Japan.
See, you get it!
Now, let's go, you guys!
We'll break that veil before
Nanami-san gets back!
Let's rescue Satoru Gojo!
Did you hear that, Awasaka?
"Satoru Gojo has been sealed."
They're leaking information
to their enemies.
What's wrong with that, Old Ogami?
It's finally starting to feel real to me.
Satoru Gojo really has been sealed.
I'm getting excited.
I wonder what's going to
happen to this country now.
Nothing new.
People will curse, be cursed, and die.
Madam, did you hear?
They said the Gojos' little
Satoru-kun was sealed!
Oh, my!
I always thought that would
happen to that boy one day!
He was always flaunting his style,
acting like he was nothing
but leg below his nipples!
Next time, "Seance"!
Next Episode
Seance
Oh, Geto-san, did you hear? The Gojos' little—